Kachi Oghenefegor Umukoro

I am a designer focused on building brands and creating digital experiences.

■ umukoro.fegor@gmail.com 🔰 +2347039718163

I am a detail oriented Product designer with 6+ years of experience in the Nigerian fashion industry. My achievements include running a fashion brand, production management for 6 collections designed and produced for leading Nigerian fashion brands including Payporte, increasing production capacity for a fashion house. I have extensive knowledge of brand development and strategy, I have helped brands communicate their niche, develop product range and brand positioning.

| Personal details | LinkedIn | linkedin.com/in/umukorokachi |
|---------------------|--|------------------------------|
| Employment | | |
| May 2016 - Present | Production Manager Angela Ezhe brand, Lagos The job involves but is not limited to ,overseeing the production process, ensuring production is cost effective, drawing up a production schedule, working out the human and material resources needed, drafting a timescale for the job, estimating costs and setting the quality standards, monitoring the production processes and adjusting schedules as needed. | |
| Mar 2019 - Present | Ui/Ux designer The Clairellen concept, Lagos Ux design is a vast and a multidisciplinary field that shapes the products and services we use on a daily basis. I specialize in bringing the tenets of brand identity with UX/UI to craft innovative and impactful design solutions for the modern, working out the human and material resources needed, drafting a timescale for the job, estimating costs and setting the quality standards, monitoring the production processes and Working out the human and material resources needed, drafting a timescale for the job, estimating costs and setting the quality standards, monitoring the production processes and adjusting schedules as needed as needed age. | |
| Jul 2017 - Mar 2018 | Brand intern Style concierge/ Ozinna. Com, Lagos Internship helped me understand the basics to branding and brand management and also help me set a tone to my career choices. | |
| Education | | |
| Sep 2010 - Jun 2015 | Bsc Computer Information System Babcock University, Ilisan, Ogun state | |
| Present | google Ux course Coursera | |
| Jan 2019 - Dec 2019 | Fashion diploma GMYT Fashion ACademy,Lagos | |
| Aug 2020 - Dec 2020 | Ui course Geneza school of design, Lagos | |
| Skills | Fashion design | Ux design |
| | Ux Research | Figma |

| Illustration | Pattern drafting |
|--------------------------------|------------------------|
| Brand strategy and development | Design Thinking |
| Great communication and | Problem solvina skill: |

Qualities

interpersonal skill

Ability to work with little or no supervision

Growth enthusiast